[{"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "I'm like, I am so lost -- you know what I was thinking, can I be very funny for a minute?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "And I'm going sitting here looking over at Trump, and I'm thinking, he started with her, right?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Like he has a pattern, right?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Period.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Was it the same for you?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Of course, every time you're absolute end.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I don't think anyone -- I don't anyone is going to be able to physically go here's there.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Did you ever find out there's any link between the injury you suffered there?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Did you have any idea what this was -- what was going on, what was happening to you?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "I'll be honest with you at that moment I -- I didn't even think about anything but getting to the emergency room.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Did you think then that you may die?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No, they -- about three days -- after they knew -- when I went in the emergency room the night it happened they -- you know I was telling them, I don't care if you got to saw my head open, do whatever you go to do, I want to live.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Were they confiding in you about this or was it something your family told you later?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "That was the strangest moment because I opened my eyes and there was about six or seven, maybe eight people and they have these things on your legs to keep the blood, you know, the blood flowing so people were like working on your legs and they're -- they were doing stuff with my hands.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "What was that moment hike?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "At first, you know -- again, my first 12 days I don't really remember much and I think they had a tough time at first and then as -- they know I'm a fighter so they know once I made it through that the first initial 10 days is the fighting, is the real scary period.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "How did they deal with it?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "You were to become forever the guy who died watching \"Busty Cops 3.\"", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "You know what I mean?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "The scariest thing about this form of hemorrhage, there -- you know, that's different from a brain tumor or even in an instance it's like a brain aneurysm.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Can it happen to anyone at any time?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "First day, you know, when you ask me, first I'm thinking, before I felt like what did I do to deserve this, because I've done a lot of stuff to deserve it.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Were you not thinking, what have I done to deserve all this?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Since I've been 6 years old, and I'm 47 now, so a long time.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "You've been a diabetic how long?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, here's what it is, I now was saying this during the break and I was laughing hard because it was like the Tonys, I said man, I possibly need to check my blood, I'm dying.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "And in absolute simple practical terms, what do you need to do to yourself every day as a diabetic?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes, because I've had it so long.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "All this is -- all this does is check my blood because the old way, why a lot of diabetics got sick is -- when you would test your urine, it could be from the night before.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "You are about to now just check what, exactly?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "You just pop your finger, right?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, my result right now is 119 which is really good.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "And if you get a bad result, what do you need to do?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "It's a lifelong balance, right?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "You know, for me very, very painful and I say it for this reason.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "What sort of memory does that bring back that moment?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "She's pre-diabetic.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What's happened to Raine since then?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Do you worry about it all at time?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Let me explain what happened.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Are you involved in that?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Very.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "So you've been quite smart protecting yourself?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Here's where it is -- with our band, I give this credit to Bobby and Ricky and CC growing up together.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "You made sure you got the money you should have got?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Can you still be as wild as you used to be?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Apparently it is.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Coming to one awesome part of your back catalog, which is is it now obligatory to enter a certain very special rock star club, that you have had to made a sex tape with Pamela Anderson?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "We haven't.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Got a wedding date yet?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "The New York Dolls.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Who is the special guest though?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I got to say we're going to win, come on.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Who is going to win?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "That was a Wednesday.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "What am I doing in this hell hole?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Here's what it is: Motley Crue, Poison, New York Dolls and special guest, SS.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "When do tickets go on sale?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Professionally, yes.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Is that the greatest kick you have?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Both.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "If I could tell you, here's the deal: you can either have sex for the rest of your life or perform on stage, you can't do both, which one do you take?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Is this like Sophie's choice?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to go with the rock 'n' roll, and here's why, because it will bring me sex.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Which way are you going to go?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "We all need help.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Does he need help, do you think?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "I don't think there is one.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "What's the simple quick fix for Charlie?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Does part of you worry that if Charlie is not careful that it could cost him his life?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Seriously.", "docId": "110302pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "You mean the new one?", "qSentId": 775}]